Jonatan Schultz

Date of birth: 28/09/1996 Nationality: Swedish Address: Jönköping, Sweden

Phone number: +46768378327

Email address: jonatan_schultz@hotmail.com





♣ Profile

I am a system developer with big passion for technology. I have a continuous desire to learn new methods of working, and new ways of dealing with problems. I am a passionate leader and strive to bring to the best out of my colleagues. Two Years of experience in dotnet.

Three Years of experience working with Frontend development & Quality Assurance

One year experience as a Project Coordinator & Team Lead system development

Work Experience

₩ 09/2018 - 2020 O BORÅS, SWEDEN

Deviation Handler Speed Competence AB

- Manage the WorkFlow Management System
- · Keep track of deviations
- Use system SAP to handle orders and warehouse management.

System developer Blåkläder AB

Full-Stack development using C#, TypeScript, NodeJs, React, NextJs, Azure services and more.

Quality Assurance & Testing

📛 03/2022 - PRESENT 🥎 SVENLJUNGA, SWEDEN

System Developer & Tech Lead Blåkläder AB

- Coordinate project & resource planning
- Analyze product requirements
- Write code to run and maintain software
- Quality Assurance
- Manage Release & Deployments

Education

☐ 01/2018 - 07/2018 SHANGHAI, CHINA Mandarin B2 Level LTL Mandarin School

⇔ 09/2019 - 06/2021 ⊗ BORÅS, SWEDEN
 System development .NET
 Borås Yrkeshögskola

Education

.NET Development, Web development, Databases, Application development, Project management, Agile methodology

A Skills

(i) LANGUAGES

Swedish Native
English Full
Mandarin Limited
Spanish Limited

(i) PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C#
TypeScript
CSS
HTML
SQL
XAML

(i) TOOLS AND FRAMEWORKS

Azure

REST

GIT

Agile

React

NextJS

NodeJS

Docker

Publications

jonatanschultz.com

jonatanschultz.com

Social Media





@jonatan-schultz

@exemplarisk